interiordezine.com 2006-06-15

# Interiordezine.com Privacy Policy for interior design.

| 

| 

This privacy policy tells you how we collect information when you visit this site and what we do with it. 

We may ask you for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address, occupation, hobbies and other details. Providing us with your personal information will help us to provide you with personalised content, or let you know about products and services that we think you would like to hear about. When you choose to give us personal information that we or our business partners or associates may request, we will try and tell you how we will use that information. 

You can access your personal information at any time to update, correct, add or delete any of the information you have shared with us. When the site is launched fully we will be providing all participants in the survey access to “my account” to find out your personal information.

Personal information automatically retrieved, such as site browsing patterns or purchasing patterns will only be used in aggregate form so that individuals are not identified.

The only exception where your personal information might be disclosed to third parties is where you enter a competition or register for any promotional feature through this site. In that case, information about you may be provided to advertisers for marketing purposes. However, you will be given the option at the time of entering the competition, or registering for the feature, to decline from receiving further information or further contact with us or the advertiser. 

We may be required by law to disclose information you provide. We will only make the disclosure if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so. 

Note that this site contains links to other sites not controlled by us. Those sites may not follow the same privacy policy as we do. 

We have teamed with others to provide our customers with enhanced internet services. In providing those services, our business associates or affiliates may also request personal information. We prohibit our associates/affiliates from selling or giving away our client information and we require them to have a posted privacy policy so that you may review it before providing personal information to them. 

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time.

We may set and access cookie files on your computer to allow us to collect information about your browsing patterns. You can configure your computer not to accept cookies, however this may mean that the access speed of your browser suffers as a result.

If you have any queries or concerns please e-mail [privacy@interiordezine.com](mailto:privacy@interiordezine.com) We will ensure a prompt reply. 

| 

[Site Information Contents](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information) [Company Profile](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Company_Profile) [Our Privacy Policy](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Our_Privacy_Policy) [Our Website Terms of Use](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Our_Website_Terms_of_Use) [Enquiry](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Enquiry) [Website Alphabetical Contents](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents) [Contents A](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_a) [Contents B](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_b) [Contents C](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_c) [Contents D](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_d) [Contents E](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_e) [Contents F](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_f) [Contents G](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_g) [Contents H](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_h) [Contents I](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_i) [Contents J](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_j) [Contents K](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_k) [Contents L](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_l) [Contents M](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_m) [Contents N](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_n) [Contents O](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_o) [Contents P](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_p) [Contents Q](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_q) [Contents R](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_r) [Contents S](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_s) [Contents T](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_t) [Contents V](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_v) [Contents W](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_w) [Contents Y](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_y) [Contents Z](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Site_Information/Contents_z) [Comprehensive Curtain Information Website](http://www.curtains.interiordezine.com/) [Color for Interior Decorating Website](http://www.color.interiordezine.com/) [Classic Modern Furniture Website](http://www.modernfurnituredesigners.interiordezine.com/) [NEW! Continuous supply of fabulous up to date articles on home improvement and makeovers](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Products/headline_home_improvement) [The latest and greatest home decorating articles](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Products/headline) [Articles on house and garden](http://www.interiordezine.com/index.cfm/Products/headline_home_garden)  
---|---|---
